{
    "subject": "resource/A_Price_Above_Rubies",
    "predicate": "property/editing",
    "object": "Arthur Coburn",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Coburn edited 'A Price Above Rubies'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.82230144739151,
            "question": "Who edited the book 'A Price Above Rubies'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6526082158088684,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the content of 'A Price Above Rubies'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5900048613548279,
            "question": "What is the significance of Arthur Coburn's work as an editor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5894249677658081,
            "question": "When was 'A Price Above Rubies' published?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.552295982837677,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a book edited by Arthur Coburn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5319859981536865,
            "question": "What is the name of the book that Arthur Coburn edited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5184664130210876,
            "question": "What genre might 'A Price Above Rubies' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4969339668750763,
            "question": "Are there any other books edited by Arthur Coburn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42037928104400635,
            "question": "What was Arthur Coburn's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41845279932022095,
            "question": "How can I find out more about Arthur Coburn and his editorial work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Coburn edited 'A Price Above Rubies'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7933_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Arthur Coburn's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7933_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other books edited by Arthur Coburn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7933_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might 'A Price Above Rubies' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7933_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7933_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not contain any information suggesting that Arthur Coburn was involved in editing the film \"A Price Above Rubies.\" There is no mention of any editor or the editorial process for this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Arthur Coburn or his involvement with the film  'A Price Above Rubies' in any of the provided text excerpts.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided about Arthur Coburn editing \"A Price Above Rubies\" in the given context.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Arthur Coburn or his role as an editor for the film.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}